You went in my...? Why would...?
What are you saying?
(Penny:)Not a big deal.
I was making coffee and ran out of milk.
(Sheldon:)You're the milk thief.
(Sheldon:)Leonard said I was crazy,
but I knew that carton felt lighter.
All right, Sheldon, calm down.
I'll call the building manager.
(Penny:)He'll come open your door.
Just eat here while you're waiting.
Eat my dinner in your apartment?
- Yeah, why not?
- Sure, why not?
(Sheldon:)And after the sun's down,
we can all pile in my pickup...
(Sheldon:)...and go skinny-dipping
down at the crick.
Because today's the day
that stopped making sense.
- Thanks.
- I'm telling you, Leonard.
Video slots, free drinks brought to us
by a bosomy barmaid...
...and all-you-can-eat shrimp for 3.95?
(Raj:)Disneyland can suck it.